Everyone's driven by something.
Rush is a drama, action film directed by Ron Howard.
In the 1970s, a rivalry propels race car drivers Niki Lauda and James Hunt to
fame and glory — until a horrible accident threatens to end it all.
James Hunt, played by Chris Hemsworth.
Niki Lauda, played by Daniel Brühl.
Suzy Miller, played by Olivia Wilde.
Marlene Lauda, played by Alexandra Maria Lara.
Clay Regazzoni, played by Pierfrancesco Favino.
Louis Stanley, played by David Calder.
Rush is a 2013 biographical sports film directed by
Ron Howard and written by Peter Morgan.
It is centred on the rivalry between two Formula One drivers, James
Hunt and Niki Lauda, during the 1976 Formula One season.
The film stars Chris Hemsworth as Hunt and Daniel Brühl as Lauda.
The film premiered in London on 2 September 2013 and was shown at the 2013 Toronto
International Film Festival before its United Kingdom release on 13 September 2013.
The film received positive reviews from critics for Hemsworth and Brühl's performances,
Howard's direction, the racing sequences, and Hans Zimmer's musical score.
The film explores themes of car race, sports, world
champion, based on true story, racing.
The tone is emotional.